websitemarketingplan.com 2017-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Marketing Plan Information, Sample Marketing Plan and Marketing Strategies

## Website Marketing Plan .com, [Web Marketing Place](http://www.webmarketingplace.com/), and [ My Online Wedding Help .com](http://www.myonlineweddinghelp.com/) Privacy Statement

### **Information Use**

Individual information is used to deliver requested newsletter, products, or services. _Aggregate information_ (in the form of statistics) is used as input in developing new products and services; to improve upon existing products and services; to decide upon marketing activities; and to generally describe our site visitors and customer base.

**We do not sell, rent, or otherwise share personal information** for advertising purposes and will never sell or give away personal information to third parties for purposes of building contact lists.

### Registration

During use of this Website, a user may complete a registration or subscription form. During registration/subscription a user give[s] contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about newsletter, products, or services on our site **for which he has expressed** __**interest.** In some instances, products or services are supplied by other sites. These sites may not use users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

### Log Files

Like most standard Websites we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. **IP addresses, etc.** **are not linked to personally identifiable information**.

### Cookies

WebSiteMarketingPlan.com uses cookies to avoid repeating some advertising messages to returning visitors. We do **not** use cookies to develop individual profiles. You are not required to accept cookies when viewing WebsiteMarketingPlan.com, WebMarketingPlace.com, or MyOnlineWeddingHelp.com. If you are concerned about cookies, you have the option of setting your browser to block or prompt for cookies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Business Transitions

In the event WebsiteMarketingPlan.com, WebMarketingPlace.com, or MyOnlineWeddingHelp.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

### Communications from the Site

### Newsletter

The primary means of communication from the site is via the newsletter. When a user wishes to subscribe to the newsletter we ask for contact information such as email address. We send all new subscribers a welcoming email that includes unsubscribe instructions.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and service announcements may opt-out of receiving these communications by sending an email to unsubscribe@WebSiteMarketingPlan.com with “unsubscribe” in the subject line. The subscriber may also contact us via postal mail at 483 S. Kirkwood Road, #113, St. Louis, MO 63122.

### Special Offers and Updates

Information on products, services and/or special deals is included in the body of each newsletter. Unsubscribe instructions are included in each newsletter.

### Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our site is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. These communications are not promotional in nature. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their subscription.

### Sharing, Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information _when required by law_ wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Website.

### Surveys

From time-to-time we may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is **completely voluntary** and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically may include contact information (to notify winners in the case of surveys with monetary awards), demographic, and other information. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys, they may not use users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

### Links

This Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Website Marketing Plan.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. _This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website_.

### **Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Email: [bkyle@websitemarketingplan.com](mailto:bkyle@websitemarketingplan.com)  
Postal Mail: Web Marketing Place LLC  
483 S. Kirkwood Road, #113  
St. Louis, MO 63122  
Telephone: 314-842-1446
